Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
The hero's name was Lumiere Silvamillion Clover.
He was later hailed as the first Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Hey there! Guess I survived. Though, as you can see, I'm a bit smaller now.
Yami, I'm leaving the rest to you now.
Okay, hold on. What kind of wacky plot twist is this?
You gave a fancy final speech and everything. Why aren't you dead?
Thinking you were dead inspired me. Now I feel like I wasted my energy.
Please relax, Yami. I'm sorry for being useless while the Clover Kingdom was in such awful peril.
I was expecting my magic to kick in sooner, but no such luck.
Oh yeah?
That's right. I'd previously stored about 13 years of time into a magic item.
I had to take a gamble, though, on whether or not it would activate.
Damn it. You're still as baddy as ever.
On the other hand, I thought I'd never see your face again, so...
Guess it isn't all bad.
Please forgive me, Julius. What I did... was foolish.
William Vangeance?
Regardless of what your reason was, betraying the kingdom is a grave crime.
Countless people have suffered, and it will take some time for them to recover.
While they're healing, I'm not going to allow you to sit idly.
Don't you think you're going a little easy on Goldy Guts there?
He did a lot of damage. The least you can do is punish him for it.
Well, the way I see it, I was the one who invited him to join the Magic Knights and made him a captain.
Which means I'm somewhat responsible.
Not only that, but I lost against the other soul that was possessing his body, the leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
I'm sure some will resent you for your part in all of this, William.
But I know your own suffering was also great.
The question is, do you have the resolve to press on, in spite of the hatred you're sure to face?
I won't fail you again, Julius. If you'll have it, then my grimoire belongs to you for the good of the Clover Kingdom.
For crying out loud, Julius. Apart from that baby face, you haven't changed one bit, have you?
With the
subjects
The
Key
Like,全てを振り払うように
叶えよう約束通り
君は出た世界だ
Let's die in this world
Even I can't up front this world
All I need is getting strong
We can catch the game
負けないでろ
Baddy up to last minute
We can catch the game
レイアルシナスヨプロドローリー
ソノカゲはミンナイダー
We can catch the game
レイアルシナスヨプロドローリー
Now then
I thank you all for your hard work
The battle has ended
And we can live happily ever after
At least that's what I'd like to say
But unfortunately
We're currently faced with three problems
Who does this guy think he is
Calling us here
He looks like a snotty little kid
I could swear I've sensed this mana before
Hang on
I know that key
Yeah
I recognize him
Let me explain problem number one
The Wizard King is nowhere to be found
You're the Wizard King genius
Or did you forget already
I knew it
Sadly my magic is mostly depleted at this point
My grimoire is just one page
So I'm unable to fight
Not only that
But I now have significantly less influence
With the hardline nobles
Whose primary concern
Is the wealth and power of this kingdom
Luke can I ask you one question
Why are you still alive
And how did you get so tiny
That was two questions
Shortstack
Ah yes
You see
One day while I was out wandering incognito
I discovered some magic technology left behind by ancient mages
According to the documents in the palace library
The device is called Swallowtail
I soon realized that my time magic and Swallowtail were very compatible
That was when I began stockpiling small amounts of magic and time
Inside the emblem on my forehead
Just in case something terrible were to happen to me
I would have the ability to start over again
However I didn't get to restart from where I'd left off
I stored only enough time to get me to this age
Even the best laid plans as they say
I'd still call that a win
Not everyone's lucky enough to get a do-over in life
Be glad you baby-faced grandpa
Secray we did it
We finally finished our first prototype
This puts us one step closer to the peaceful world you want to create
It's all thanks to you
You seem to believe your type of magic isn't good for anything
But that's just not true
Prince
Oh and I've already come up with a name for our new magic item
But for now it'll be a secret
Secray Swallowtail
Your Highness
Our creation has survived for all these years
And now it's saved the life of a person who carries your legacy
This whole thing is weird and confusing but I'm just happy to see you're still alive Wizard King
Thanks Asta
You're as energetic as ever
I hear you did a great job once again
I've got a long way to go sir but yeah I gave it my best
As for Noelle and Mimosa
I can tell by the growth of your mana that you courageously risked your lives in this endeavor
Well done both of you
Thank you
And lastly to our guest whom I don't recognize
Tell me about your magic
I spent so many years wandering all over this land in disguise
And I've never even heard of anything like your power
Chill out you still haven't finished explaining everything
Now hurry up and fill us in so we can go and help the others
Oh right sorry about that
So he hasn't changed at all then
Yeah that's his default
Excitable as always
You planning to tell us about problems two and three anytime soon?
I'm doing my best to keep them a secret for as long as possible
But I will say this
I fear that the Clover Kingdom is going to be attacked by the neighboring lands
You mean
The Diamond Kingdom right?
Like before
Also,there's a possibility that Asta will die
ASTA could Die?
Did I miss something here?
Hang on is this an either-or situation or what because both of those things sound really bad?
Actually they could both happen
And his predictions are usually spot on
I'm glad I'm not you
Farewell
I'm still planning my funeral yet?
could you back up and explain this better please asta the dark power that you've been using came
from a devil what is that true like that creepy guy we just fought i mean it does have kind of
the same feel whenever i use it but a devil of course that other form of his it is similar to
the one our grandmother told us about when we were little knowing that i wonder if it's too
dangerous for you to use that power what do you mean i'm totally fine it's only a little excruciating
pain that's all nothing about what you just said sounds fine to me a devil huh ugh gross stay away
did you mean that the way it sounded because it was really hurtful that horn is a symbol of when
humans ventured into another realm and got themselves involved in a world beyond our own
it's a curse known as wegg apparently there are other magic knights who suffer from similar
conditions wait you mean i'm not the only one i'm confused what realm are you talking about sir
i don't know all of the details but they say it's where the devils reside indeed and the five leaf
grimoire that one devil failed to get his hands on was eventually claimed by another of this kind
are you she has horns as well 500 years back i was cursed by forbidden magic while sealing him
then the evil curse and my own magic were mixed together which caused this to happen
i can change between my two forms as often as i please now
how neat this is entirely different than transformation magic you're sealing yourself
into the form of that tiny bird to think the penalty for using forbidden magic combined with
your rare affinity would produce a result like this ancient magic is so fascinating can we get back to
me tell me the truth am i seriously about to die what if the devil explodes and i end up in pieces oh
right sorry as you may be aware the clover kingdom is surrounded by three other nations
the diamond kingdom is aggressive thanks to their magic scholars their army is strong and they're known
to experiment on humans then there's the neutral kingdom of heart their land is rich with natural mana
so the people mostly keep to themselves focused on perfecting their own unique magic the last is the
spade kingdom which is currently vying for dominance it's a frigid demonic landscape served by the
ancient evils that sleep within they don't share a border with us like the diamond kingdom does so
spade wants to extend its influence across the strong magic region between us but due to recent events
the magic knights who defend our land are more exhausted than ever before yeah and let's not
forget about the ones who got possessed and switch sides on us the powers that be won't take too kindly
to that and then there's our widow wizard king wait that's not fair they can't help it if they
were taken over by the elves it doesn't mean that they can't be trusted don't you remember this guy
it's his fault everything's so screwed up see if we tell everyone that they'll understand then the
magic knights won't get in trouble that's true but someone must pay so the magic parliament will likely
blame your devil's power they'll do everything they can to find it guilty after all you're a commoner
who can use a dark and mysterious power which makes you the perfect scapegoat for this ordeal
no way that doesn't make sense i didn't do anything wrong and what even is the magic parliament wow
you're more ignorant than i thought well it's a group they're mostly royalty and nobles they create
the laws and hold trials for major crimes it's one of the highest authorities in the land that's right
and it's controlled by one of the three great royal families house kira the current king's family they
have the most power of anyone you're my hero you've done an excellent job of protecting me
seki brunzaza of the green praying mantises you have my gratitude
oh you sure are brave for a lonely commoner so this is what julius was talking about when he said
their potential could be found in the most unlikely of places come to think of it all of you praying
mantises are commoners and your captain was downright insane the man's insufferable but still
you did well he's on his rocker all hell broke loose in the royal capital so i was trying to leave
oh no it's the king please don't be dead i'll be charged with ha-ha homicide the whole thing was a huge
coincidence your majesty thanks to my newly discovered power it was a piece of cake for me to save you no
gratitude necessary what a stalwart young lad my luck's been awful ever since i met that brat at the
entrance exam but now things are finally starting to go my way i was born under a lucky star
there he is there's a magic knight with him but it's one of the lower ranking ones so i doubt he'll
give us much trouble this won't take long augustus kira surrender now we've come for your life
who had the nerve to send you dogs here well that was fun while it lasted you don't need to know
either way the eye of the midnight sun will be blamed for it
what why did my weapon shrink shameful it's so like you anti-monarchist nobles to take advantage
of a disaster to harm the king your fiends all of you now kneel
what kind of magic does he have i can't move you're from house kira are you all right my liege i am
all right my royal rooms are filthy yes my apologies look at that it's finally appeared mark my words i'll
condemn you for the sake of justice and the royal family devil possessed wretch
several days later nozel and fuegolion led the effort to steadily rebuild the royal capital after it had
been decimated by the elves attack the people were finally beginning to smile again as for asta and his
friends hey chow down as much as you want everybody charmy's food will bring all your mana back in no time
huh oh you must be asta right i heard you were great in the big fight the other day hi mono to meet you
wow thanks it was nothing really sorry do i know you oh i suppose not i should have mentioned i work
with the magic parliament hey that's what the wizard king told us about if you wouldn't mind we'd like
you to come testify for us about the battle so we can get the honest truth the honest truth yes that's
our job after all oh the mysterious girl we'd be very interested in your testimony as well miss yeah
let's do it narrow you can tell this is a trap right don't worry noel he seems like he's a totally
reasonable person besides someone needs to tell them what happened with the devil and that whole
reincarnation thing and who better to do it than us right please go ahead inside okay now that we're
here i'm starting to get really nervous remember what the wizard king said about your devil's power
don't let your guard down we got the elves to listen to us as long as they let us talk it'll be fine
handcuffs what gives i don't recognize this he's so loud and vulgar they were right to put that
ruffian in handcuffs the clover kingdom's just and honorable magic parliament is now in session
as your humble chairman i domnatio kira shall pass judgment upon asta of the black bulls
hold on this isn't fair you can't just treat us like we're criminals
looks like we fell right into their trap well that's no surprise i always knew that raucous
little beast was up to no good i couldn't have said it better myself whatever he did he's about
to face the consequences how dare you commit such a terrible crime after i let you join the royal knights
asta of the black bulls raised in the church in haj village which lies in the forsaken realm
you're an orphan and i don't feel an ounce of magic from you the forsaken realm oh my filthy little
commoner and as for the young lady look she's got horns the kingdom has no record of her birth and
those horns indicate she has dabbled in forbidden magic forbidden magic she deserves to die these
two claim that the recent disturbance was caused by a devil who ensnared and controlled a number of
magic knights that's right the magic knights only did all that stuff because a devil was forcing them
too devil you say this story is much more involved than i thought we can't trust those commoners he's a
black bull the least respectable of all the squads she's got horns that means she sold himself to the
devil no doubt about it wizard king julius worked so hard and yet these people are still so hateful
even asta's belief that we can all understand each other is fading now these nobles aren't used to
hearing from people who are different than them listen to me would you i'm telling you the truth
this trial will end in one of two ways either you will be convicted as a devil or the magic knights will
be made to atone for the countless sins they have committed and you clearly can't abandon others
according to the scales you're simple-minded and therefore easily dealt with a single commoner
or the magic knights who protect our home it's obvious which way the scales will tip
unless you can tell us where this devil is now he's gone we defeated him i told you that
all because narrow worked hard for a really long time to make it happen unfortunately every person in
this room suspects that you and this girl are the ones who've been communicating with the devil
they're wrong i can explain the one inside my grimoires whatever you say is just going to get
twisted it's too risky to tell them about your power well if there isn't a devil then we'll have to
exact judgment on everyone who was involved bring her in
marie
asta
this is marie adlai cast out from the house adlai this ruined ex noble now makes her home in a
church among orphans her older brother gauche is a former convict we have confirmed that during the
recent battle in question her eye magic indirectly caused great harm to magic knights as well as some
of the citizenry you're making stuff up marie didn't do any of those bad things on purpose perhaps
you're right if a devil truly did play a part in all this i might believe the girl was coerced
however if you cannot provide any proof all that remains is the fact of her crimes therefore
she must pay the price justice will be served
no stop
i declare you guilty
you don't have the right to judge anybody
what's he doing you monster you have no idea what real justice is
i think this trial is over
we don't reason with devils
so
yuri
me
The page is now open
I'm not afraid
I'm in front of you
I'm strong enough
I'm going to fly
Just take my hand
I'm living with you
I'm waiting for you